纽约州北部
11月27日
UPSTATE NEWYORK
NOVEMBER27
- 我们本该开本田来的
- 我们把行李放口哪
- We should have taken the Honda.
- Where would we have put the luggage?
你非常强壮
You're very strong.
这是我跟你在一起的最后一个假期
This is the last holiday .I’m ever going on with you.
你从哪里练就的那些肌肉？再用力！不要放松
Where did you get all those muscles? More! Don't quit now.
- 还要多远
- 几百万英里
- How much further?
- A couple of million miles.
- 什么
- 几百万英里
- What?
- A couple of million miles.
不，到那上面我们就停
No, up here we'll stop.
下次，墨西哥
夏威夷更好
- Mexico, next time.
- Hawaii is better.
停。好了
Hold it. That's good.
现在怎么办
我会找帮手
- Now what?
- I'll try to get us some help.
来吧，让我们打一场雪仗。
Come on, let's have a snowball fight.
不
No!
帮我，爸爸
Help me, Daddy.
你有道路突发事件服务中心的号码吗？
Do you have the number for emergency road service?
片名：夺魂冤灵
THE CHANGELING
如果你想要办什么事，只要喊我一声，拉塞尔先生
If you want a hand with anything,
just give me a shout, Mr. Russell.
拉塞尔先生
Mr. Russell?
爸爸
Daddy.
接住
Catch.
拉塞尔先生
Mr. Russell...
你知道这个球也要带大西雅图去
You know that this piece is going to Seattle, too.
是的，先生
好的
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
西雅图3月4日
SEATTLE - MARCH 4TH
开始，我惊呆了
At first, I was in shock.
我机械地反应着，亳无知觉
I just functioned automatically.
I didn't feel anything.
然后有一天我猛然刺痛，凯西走了
Then one day it hit me: Joanna and Kathy are gone.
我在住所周围走来走去，我猜我是半颠半痴
I kept walking around the apartment.I guess I was half crazy.
那是四个月前，我不得不振作起来
That was four months ago. I've got to start making demands on myself.
你的第一节课在下个周一，我已经成立里了教职工会议
Your first class is next Monday.I’ve set up a faculty meeting.
11点钟你方便吗？
好的，感谢你做的一切
- Is eleven okay for you?
- Fine, thanks for everything.
你到这里来我们都很兴奋
We're all excited about you being here.
一个著名的校友作曲家
A well-known alumnus and distinguished composer.
你来了我们很高兴
We're glad you came.
好了，孩子们，不要玩了。去吃点东西
Okay, kids, keep it down.Go and get yourselves some cookies.
你不必住旅馆，有很多房子供你住
You don't need to stay in that hotel.There's plenty of room for you here.
我去找家出租房，我有一些东西要出版
I’m going to find a house to rent.I’ve got some things coming out.
我需要一个放得下钢琴可以工作的地方
I need a place I can pound away at the piano. A place I can work.
我的朋友在历史文物保护协会工作
My friend works for the Historical Preservation Society.
他们有旧房子租。我看她能找到什么样的
They have old houses for rent.We'll see what she can come up with.
拉塞尔先生
是的
- Mr. Russell?
- Yes.
我是克莱尔·诺曼，进来我们一起坐车
I’m Claire Norman. Hop in and we'll drive up.
这房子几年没有人住
大概有12年
- When was the house last occupied?
- About 12 years ago.
过去12年房子一直是历史协会的
It's been with the Historical Society for the past 12 years.
我们走那边
There we go.
我们计划把它改成博物馆
There were plans to turn it into a museum.
但是我猜这房子是用来住人的
But I guess the house was meant to be lived in.
为什么还没有人住
我去年加入协会的
- Why hasn't it been lived in?
- I joined the society last year.
我想他们在这栋房子没花功夫
I don't think they've tried very hard with this place.
当然它需要很多整修工作
Of course it does need a lot of work.
这里有几件东西是刚搬进来的
There are some pieces here that are just stored.
你可以自己挑选，随便你喜欢
You'd have your pick of them.Whatever you like.
保修这么大的房子要花什么昵
What does it take to maintain a house of this size?
我们有保修工，塔特尔先生
We have a maintenance man.Mr. Tuttle.
还有...这是音乐房
And... this is the music room.
这是我把你和这个房间想到一起的真正原因
This is really why I thought of you and this house.
协会接手时钢琴留在了这里
The piano was left here when the society took over.
它肯定不好使了
It must be in very bad shape.
这些是什么
What are the terms?
很抱歉打扰你作曲
这是已经谱好的 曲子
- Sorry to disturb your composing.
- This has already been composed.
门前有个人手里拿着蓄水槽
There's a man at the front with a water-storage tank.
有没有写大作
我还在写第二乐章
- Manage to do any writing?
- I’m still on the second movement.
讲座可能给你一点灵感
The lectures may give you some ideas.
按我的理解
It’s my understanding...
...有23个学生报了名
...that there are 23 students registered
参加这种高级音乐形式的系列讲座
- for this series of lectures on advanced musical form.
外面没有下雨
It’s not raining outside...
除非建筑的其它地方着火了
And unless there's afire in some other part of the building...
这里有很多人没有更好的事情可做
...there are an awful lot of people here with nothing better to do.
但是，第二次讲座后我们将知道更多
However, we'll know moreafter the second lecture.
我敢肯定你们当中很多人会认识到这一点
I’m sure there are many of you who may recognize this.
管弦乐队听起来好些
你在课堂上奏得动听
- It sounds better with an orchestra.
- You made it sound fine in class.
约翰的秘密是他是个天才
John's secret is that he's a natural ham.
如果你找不到归路
我会派个寻人派对
- If you can't find your way back...
- I'll send out a search party.
Hi ，我想让你见见我母亲
你好 诺曼女士
- Hi, I'd like you to meet my mother.
- How do you do, Mrs. Norman?
这是约翰，切斯曼公寓
This is John Russell.The Chessman House.
见到你我非常高兴，你喜欢那房子吗？
I’m very pleased to meet you.How are you liking the place?
还好
那房子好大
- Fine.
- It’s so large.
请听我说好吗
May I have your attention please?
我想介绍下，这是卡尔迈克尔议员
I’d like to introduce Senator Carmichael.
他将再做一次演讲
He's going to make another speech.
一个终生共和党人评论民主党
A lifelong Republican commenting on a Democrat.
你们知道我不喜欢演讲，但特殊情况除外...
You know how I hate making speeches.But on special occasions...
比如为我们的交响管乐队集资
...like raising money for our Symphony Orchestra...
今晚太美貌了，不是吗
Weren't they fantastic tonight?
我去拿点喝的
我想跟你去
- I’m going to get a drink.
- I think I'll join you.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
谢谢
Thank you.
他儿子是我们历史文物保护协会的董事
He's on our Board of Directors at the Historical Preservation Society.
他是我们这里最大的慈善家
He's our number one philanthropist.
你渐渐习惯了吗
是的
- You're getting settled in then?
- Yes.
协会里还有一些东西
Some pieces are still at the society.
我看能不能帮你弄来
I'll see if I can dig them up for you.
我很高兴你租下那栋房子
I’m glad you took the house.
塔特尔先生
Mr. Tuttle?
是的 ，Mr 拉塞尔
你吓我一跳
- Yes, Mr. Russell.
- You frightened me.
这里还有其他人吗
没有，先生。只有我一个
- Is anyone else here?
- No, sir. Just me.
很悦耳，那音乐
That's lovely, the music.
有催眠的效果
就是催眠曲
- It has the quality of a lullaby.
- It is.
我们来了，我们说过要来
Here we are, as promised.
这是以前刚在房子里的混合印刷物
These are some assorted prints that used to hang in the house.
这是张旧的修补房子后景照
This is an old, restored photograph taken from the back of the house.
我想打电话 但信号说你的号码没有登记
I tried to call, but information isn't giving your number out.
那是件好家具，你有没有修？
That's a beautiful piece.Did you refinish it?
没有
I didn't, no.
那是凯西的，我女儿的
That was Kathy's, my daughter's.
我要走了，希望你喜欢这些画
I’d better be off.I hope you like the prints.
你骑马吗
对，你也骑马吗
- Are you going riding?
- Yes. Do you ride?
约翰 怎么了
John, what's the matter?
我想起了我女儿凯西
I was thinking about my daughter Kathy.
她多爱马呀
How much she loved horses.
是气闸 ，不知在哪
声音太大 ，太有节奏了
- An airlock, somewhere.
- It was too loud, too rhythmic.
至少它启动了
Well, it's starting at least.
它持续了两个早上了而且正好6点
It’s happened two mornings in a row,precisely at 6 o'clock.
声音持续大概半分钟然后停了，一片死寂
It goes on for about half a minute and then stops dead.
锅炉跟其它东西一样，有自己的习惯
A furnace is like anything else.It’s got habits.
这是老房子 老房子会有声音的
It’s an old house. It makes noises.
很好
Very good.
我们断拍不统一
We're not together on the off-beats.
先生，你要求太多了，否则就会觉得很好
Don, you're retarding too much, otherwise it was splendid.
晚安
Good night.
历史协会
HISTORICAL SOCIETY
以前有过这样的事吗？如果发生 采取了什么措施
Has anything like this happened before? If so, what was done about it?
自从我加入协会房子一直空着
Since I’ve been with the society,the house has been empty.
你现在工作很辛苦，又有了情感疲劳
You're working very hard.You've been through emotional strain.
我现在会产生幻觉，那就是你要说的吗？
I’m hallucinating.Is that what you're going to say?
有个电话找你，你妈的，要告诉她你忙吗
There's a call for you. Your mother.Should I tell her you're busy?
对不起 约翰
Excuse me, John.
你的租房有问题 拉塞尔先生
There's some question about your lease, Mr. Russell.
那栋房子不能出租的，诺曼小姐没有仔细看文件
That house shouldn't have been rented.Miss Norman rushed the papers through.
她没有通过正当的途径
为什么有反对
- She did not use proper channels.
- Why should anyone object?
那栋房子不适合住人
That house is not fit to live in.
没有人能够在那里住下去
No one has been able to live in it.
它不欢迎人
于是原先麻烦不断
- It doesn't want people.
- Then there has been trouble before.
C.S.B.1909年1月
C.S.B.JANUARY 1909
克莱尔，你听，音阶相符，速度和音调都一样
Claire, listen. It’s note for note.Same tempo and even the same key.
你认为有什么
我不知道
- What do you think?
- I don't know.
是个惊人的巧合
It’s a startling coincidence.
但是那一定是流行音乐，否则不会在音乐盒里
But that must be a popular melody,or it wouldn't be on the music box.
我同意 ，但我以前从未听过那天你来的时候我演奏了
I agree, but I never heard it before I played it that day you came over.
不，其中必有蹊跷
No, there's something!
这样的事这里以前发生过，我不是第一个
It’s happened before here.I’m not the first.
我仔细阅了档案，一直追溯到1920年
I went over the files very carefully,all the way back to 1920.
一切正常
贺婿礼小姐
- Nothing out of the ordinary.
- Miss Huxley...
米尼是个性格古怪的老女人，但是她从未
Minnie's a highly eccentric old woman,but she'd never...
她说这个房子不欢迎人，她错了
She said the house didn't want people.She's mistaken.
不管是什么都不顾一切的想交流什么
Whatever it is is trying desperately to communicate.
重击，水龙头，破碎的窗玻璃
The banging, the water taps,the broken window panes.
一切发生的事都是为了把我带到阁楼
Everything that's happened was designed to get me into the attic.
我想看看
I want to see it.
你看桌上的书
Look at that book on the desk.
C.S.B.1909年1月4日
C.S.B. January 4th, 1909.
是小孩子的字迹
It’s a little child's writing.
1909 ，那时谁会住在这里昵
1909.Who could have lived here then?
我在壁炉架上找到那个音乐盒
I found the music box on the mantel.
看这轮椅
Look at this wheelchair.
我的天！这么小
My God! It’s so small.
这间房子做什么用的
What was this room?
前居住者，威廉·萨拉奇诺及其一家
Former residents,William Saracino and family...
...1965年买下，1967年卖出
...bought the place in 1965,sold it in 1967.
1967年协会买下了，是卡尔迈克尔基金买下的
Purchased for the society in 1967,by the Carmichael Foundation.
是议员
是的
- That's the senator?
- Yes.
档案在哪儿
没有列出前面的居住者
- Where is the file?
- No previous occupants listed.
1920年前什么都没有
There's nothing here before 1920.
米尼我们找切斯曼公寓1920年以前的档案
Minnie, we're looking for the Chessman House file pre-1920.
你想知道些什么
1909年谁住那儿
- What do you want to know?
- Who lived there in 1909?
一个叫巴纳德的先生
他有孩子吗
- A Dr. Barnard.
- Did he have any children?
一个儿子一个女儿
A son and a daughter.
发生了家庭悲剧，1909年他把房子卖了
There was some kind of family tragedy.He sold the house in 1909.
1909 我为你建立档案
1909. I'll set it up for you.
一切准备好了，预览器在右边
It’s all ready to go.The scanner is on the right.
我们在这里看看
Let's have a look here.
2月9日。这些是招租广告，财政版
February 9th. These are want ads.Financial page.
房地产 ，更多招租广告
Real estate. More want ads.
等下
Wait.
科拉巴纳德 沃尔特 巴纳德医生九岁的女儿
"Cora Barnard, seven-year-old daughter of Dr. Walter Barnard...
当她在一辆载煤的车子前面奔跑时 被严重撞伤
...was seriously injured when she ran in front of a passing coal cart. "
她被送往医院但医治无效
"She was taken to hospital where her condition remains grave. "
因此不久后...
So forth and so on...
科拉巴纳德..C.S.B
Cora Bernard... C.S.B.
这里
There.
科拉斯蒂华德 巴纳德..
"Cora Steward Barnard...
...由于2月15日的事故中受伤,长眠地下
...succumbed to injuries sustained in a February 15th accident. "
她的父母沉重哀悼，并将她埋在家庭墓区里
"She is mourned by her parents and will be interred in a family plot. "
那是博士和他妻子
There's the doctor and his wife.
那是哥哥,劳埃德
There's the brother, Lloyd.
这个小女孩,科拉，死于街头
This little girl, Cora,was killed in the street.
是一次事故，跟凯西几乎一样
It was an accident,almost the same as Kathy.
那房间里的是什么
What is in that house?
它在干什么？为什么想要告诉我？
What is it doing? Why is it trying to reach me?
是不是因为我女儿？我不能再次经受痛苦
Is it because of my daughter? I can't go through all this again.
约翰,你必须离开那栋房子
John, you must get out of that house.
我相信你说的一切
I believe everything you're saying.
噪音,灯光，物体的心灵运输
The noises, the lights,the teleportation of objects.
这是非常有趣的事
但是现在我怎么做
- It’s all fascinating stuff.
- But what do I do now?
我告诉你,是花边新闻
I'll tell you, off the record...
我们有很多方法，我们检验过很多术士
We have many mediums and spiritualists coming here and we test them.
99%纯属骗人
99 percent are utter frauds.
但是有1%很令人吃惊
But the one percent... astonishing.
一种方法
A medium.
拉塞尔先生,你好，我妻子,利亚
Mr. Russell, how do you do? My wife, Leah.
请进
Go right in, please.
我们把灯调暗点吧
Could we have the lights off, please?
我可以录下发生的事吗
当然可以
- May I record what happens?
- Yes, of course.
拉塞尔先生，请你坐这儿好吗
我坐那儿。谢谢
Mr. Russell, would you sit there?
And I'll sit here. Thank you.
你受苦了，约翰·拉塞尔，你失去了妻子和孩子
You've suffered, John Russell.You've lost a wife and child.
这栋房子发生的是冲着你那失去而来的
The presence in this house is reaching out to you through that loss.
这里的冤灵很强
The presence is very strong here.
是一个孩子的冤灵，一个孩子灵魂不安
It is a child's presence.A child who is not at peace...
...不能安息
...who cannot rest.
冤灵正跟我们在一起
The presence is with us.
我们感觉到你在身边
We sense that you are with us.
你能跟我们说话吗？
Will you talk with us?
跟我们交流好吗？
Will you communicate with us?
你能向我们倾诉吗？
Will you come through to us?
能不能跟我们说话？
Will you speak to us?
我们是来这里帮你的
We are here to help you.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
能跟我们说话吗？
Will you speak to us?
能
Yes.
你叫什么名字？你是那个叫科拉的小孩吗？
What is your name? Are you the child, Cora?
你是被煤车撞死的小孩吗？
Are you the child killed by the coal cart?
不
No.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
约瑟夫
Joseph.
你是在这里死的，约瑟夫？
Did you die in this house, Joseph?
怎么死的
How did you die?
这里有你想要交谈的人吗？
Is there someone here you wish to communicate with?
约翰
John.
救命
Help.
救命，约翰
Help, John.
救命
Help.
拉塞尔先生，你能做到这里来吗
Mr. Russell, will you sit over here?
你能不能跟约翰说？
Will you speak to John?
能不能告诉我们你为什么不能瞑目？
Will you tell us why you are not at rest?
跟约翰说话
Speak to John.
约翰跟我们在一起
John is with us.
你要约翰做什么？
What do you want of John?
为什么你感到不安？
Why do you feel no peace?
为什么你还在这栋房子里？
Why do you remain in this house?
这栋房子里有什么？
What is in this house?
跟约翰说话
Speak to John.
约翰跟我们在一起
John is with us.
你是怎么死的？
How did you die?
是在这栋房子里死的？
Did you die in this house?
为什么你还在这栋房子里，约瑟夫？
Why do you remain in this house, Joseph?
约瑟夫，是在这栋房子里死的？
Joseph, did you die in this house?
我们是来这里帮你的
We are here to help you.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
...你是被煤车撞死的小孩吗？
... killed by the coal cart?
不
- No.
你是被煤车撞死的小孩吗
Are you the child killed by the coal cart?
不
- No.
你是被煤车撞死的小孩吗?
Are you the child killed by the coal cart?
不
- No.
我们是来这里帮你的，你叫什么名字
We are here to help you.What is your name?
约瑟夫
Joseph.
你叫什么名字
约瑟夫
- What is your name?
- Joseph.
约瑟夫
是在这栋房子里死的
房子
- Did you die in this house?
- House.
我房间里
My room.
不能走路
Can't walk.
告诉我们你为什么不瞑目
我爸爸
- Tell us why you are not at rest.
- My father.
是在这栋房子里死的
我房间里
- Did you die in this house?
- My room.
你怎么死的
How did you die?
爸爸
Father.
再见
Farewell.
Sacred Heart.
神圣的心
My medal.
爸爸，不要
Father, don't.
我的身体...农场...井
My body... ranch... the well.
我的名字...约瑟夫·卡尔迈克尔
My name... Joseph Carmichael.
克莱尔
Claire...
是的
Yeah.
我抱歉
I’m sorry to...
你能来一下吗
Can you come?
告诉我们你为什么不能瞑目
我爸爸
- Tell us why you are not at rest.
- My father.
你在这房子里死的
我卧室
- Did you die in this house?
- My room.
你怎么死的
爸爸，不要
- How did you die?
- Father, don't.
我叫约瑟夫·卡尔迈克尔
My name is Joseph Carmichael.
我本该叫你们的，我只是需要一个人
I shouldn't have called you.I just needed someone.
我在纸上写了东西
I wrote some words on the paper.
我写了神圣的心
I wrote Sacred Heart.
过去有个叫神圣的心的郡属孤儿院
There used to be a county orphanage named Sacred Heart.
几年前关来
It was closed down years ago.
一个孤儿院
对
- An orphanage?
- Yes.
那个小孩，约瑟夫·卡尔迈克尔...
That child, Joseph Carmichael...
他在阁楼被人谋杀
He was murdered in this house,
in the attic.
然后被埋...然后有个孤儿...
And buried... and then an orphan...
停 ，约翰！离开这里
Stop it, John!Move away from this place.
贺壻黎小姐来电话，议员，她说有要事
Miss Huxley is on the phone, Senator.She says it's important.
好的，我接
All right, I'll take it.
米尼，你好吗？
很好
- Minnie, how are you?
- Fine.
他们查阅了档案
再说下他的名字
- They've been through the files.
- Let me have that name again.
约翰·拉塞尔
John Russell.
我很高兴能帮忙
I’m very glad to be of help.
再见
Goodbye.
1960年议员竞选
The senator's campaign from 1960.
我从主图书馆得到的，你发现了什么吗？
I got it from the main library.Have you found something?
一份回顾文件，房子装修为博物馆时拟订的
A retrospective, drawn up when the house was to be turned into a museum.
理查德·卡尔迈克尔家1899-1906住这所房子
Richard Carmichael and family occupied the house 1899-1906.
理查德是议员的父亲，他母亲生产时死了
Richard was the senator's father.His mother died in childbirth.
这是他的病情的部分记载
Look at the part about his illness.
卡尔迈克尔，他儿子，三岁时患萎缩性关节炎
"Joe Carmichael, his son, at age three contracted atrophic arthritis. "
本计划送他去瑞士北部的疗养院的
"It was decided to send him to the Nordbach Sanatorium in Switzerland. "
他和他父亲1960年启程去了欧洲
"He and his father embarked for Europe in 1906."
他直到一战结束才来到美国
"He did not set foot upon American soil until the cessation of WW I."
你知道他做了什么理查德的儿子，一个生病的孩子
You see how it might have been done.Richard's son, a sick child.
他被他父亲谋杀并秘密地埋掉
He was murdered by his father and buried secretly.
一个6岁 的孤儿代替他并坐船去了海外
He was substituted by a six-year-old orphan and shipped overseas.
按照他父亲的安排为他们工作 ，甚至参战
With the father attending,it all worked for them, even the war.
1918年他回来，那时他18岁
He came back here in 1918,when he was 18 years old.
谁会知道他不是那个残疾小孩？他的地位巩固了
Who was going to know he wasn't the crippled son? He was cured.
你认为他知道谋杀和掉包的事吗？
Do you think he knows about the murder and about the replacement?
我不知道
一个父亲怎么能作出这样的事？
- I don't know.
- How could a father do such a thing?
理查德的妻子是艾米丽·斯宾塞，H.T.斯宾的女儿
Richard's wife was Emily Spencer,daughter of H.T. Spencer.
他建立了斯宾塞卡尔·迈克尔帝国，死干1905年
He founded the Spencer-Carmichael empire. He died in 1905.
他是亿万富翁，他的遗嘱可能很有趣
He was a zillionaire.His will might be very interesting.
我还会找一下有没有斯宾塞卡尔·迈克尔农场
I'll also try to find out if there was a Spencer-Carmichael ranch.
有口井农场
A ranch with a well.
这是西雅图1908年的地图集，上面有卡尔迈克尔牧场
This is the 1908 atlas of Seattle showing the Carmichael ranch.
那个小标记是什么
What is that little mark right there?
根据图例，是水井所在地
According to the legend,it was the location of a well.
在1914年的地图集中，在同样的地方开着...
In the 1914 atlas,which is opened to the same area...
...财产没有什么改变，就像水井的地点
...the property is very much the same,as is the location of the well.
在1928地图集上，随着财产的细分有了变动
In the 1928 atlas, there's a change,with subdivision of the property.
水井标志消失了，那里建起了房子
The well symbol has disappeared,and a house has been built here.
格雷女士 第13627街 西雅图 华盛顿
MRS. E. GREY 13627TH STREET, SEATTLE,WASH.
牧场列在遗嘱上
The ranch is listed in the will.
他是5岁的约瑟夫的遗产的一部分。他什么都有
It’s part of five-year-old Joseph's inheritance. He got everything.
他父亲昵
形同虚设
- What about the father?
- Bypassed.
只是不动产的监护人和管理者
Except as guardian and trustee of the estate.
这个老头的女儿死了，他不太喜欢女婿
The old man's daughter was dead, and he wasn't too fond of his son-in-law.
是 但等等...理查德没有一分钱
Yes, but wait...Richard doesn't get any money.
但是他仍然控制着儿子，他的儿子很值钱...
But he still controls his son and his son is worth a fortune...
...除非这个男孩由干某种原因在21岁前死了
...unless for some reason the boy dies before attaining the age of21.
那么房产就归慈善机构而把理查德拒之门外
Then the estate goes to charity.That would have shut Richard out.
与他一起的儿子体弱多病，卧床不起
And there he was with a son who was weak, sickly, bedridden...
他肯定决定不要在这个男孩身上下赌汪
He must have decided not to take a chance on the boy.
你要告诉她什么
关于井和男孩的事
- What are you going to tell her?
- About the well and the body.
还有上有名字的纪念章
不 ，不是讲卡尔迈克尔的事
- And the medal with the name on it?
- No, and nothing about Carmichael.
她会以为你疯了的
你可以告诉她我没疯
- She'll think you're crazy.
- You'll tell her I’m not.
晚上好，格雷女士，我是约翰·拉塞尔，这是诺曼小姐
Good evening, Mrs. Grey.I’m John Russell. This is Miss Norman.
我不该听你讲了两分钟故事
I wouldn't have listened to your story for two minutes.
我不该让你进这里，如果不是你电话里说的
I wouldn't have let you in here, but for something you said on the phone.
你说怪事发生在三天前
You said this seance affair happened three nights ago.
三天前，在周一晚上....
Three nights ago,on Monday night...
...林达，我女儿刚过子夜，就醒来大喊大叫
...Linda, my daughter, woke up screaming just after midnight.
她做了恶梦，我拥着她。她歇斯底里
She'd had a nightmare.I went in to her. She was hysterical.
我以前从未见她那样，她做过恶梦，但不是...
I’d never seen her like that before.She's had nightmares, but not...
她说 她看到一个男孩，非常小，非常瘦...
She said she'd seen a boy,very small, very thin...
...简直像树精，他想从地板上钻上来
...almost gnome-like, and he was trying to come up through the floor.
而且他一直盯着她
And he kept staring at her.
在这，中间
Here, in the middle.
自从跟我睡一起就再没到过这房间
She hasn't been in the room since.She sleeps with me.
我们想做的是...
What we want...
你想把这间房子拆掉
What you want is to tear this room apart.
我有你的电话号码，我得考虑一下
I have your phone number.I'll have to think about it.
他们还在挖，但他们已经找那口井
They're still digging,but they've found the well.
好
Okay.
找到有东西吗
还没有
- Find anything?
- Not yet.
这是托尼 格雷女士的儿子，诺曼女士
This is Tony, Mrs. Grey's son.Miss Norman.
谢谢
Thanks.
请把闪光灯绐我，好吗？
Get me the flashlight, will you?
我想我找到东西了
I think I’ve found something.
是什么
What is it?
是一只手
什么
- It’s a hand.
- What?
是只手
我去叫警察
- It’s a hand.
- I'll call the police.
没有了
不像没有
- Nothing more?
- It doesn't look like it.
可能有其它东西吗
没有
- Might there be something more?
- No.
验尸官说骨头是很陈旧了，你知道那个孩子是谁
The coroner said the bones were old.Do you know who that child was?
不，真的不是
真的不是是什么意思？
- No, not really.
- What does "not really" mean?
不
No.
我想每个人的陈词，你有住的地方吗
I want statements from everybody.Do you have somewhere else to stay?
是的，都安排好了
Yes, it's all been arranged.
我认为你本该告诉他们
必须这样
- I think you should have told them.
- It’s got to be there.
我们需要纪念章做证据
你有录音带
- We need that medal for evidence.
- You have the tape.
录音带可以修改的，他们很清楚
Tapes can be altered.They know that.
很朋显，你保留了一些东西
It was obvious you were holding something back.
很晚了，休息一下
好的，小心开车
- It’s late. Get some rest.
- Fine. Drive carefully.
什么事？
What's the matter?
圣保罗教堂，1900年9月8日
St. Paul's Church.September8th, 1900.
约瑟夫·帕特里克·卡尔迈克尔，它在那儿？
Joseph Patrick Carmichael.It wasthere?
它在那儿
It was there.
你必须交绐警察，它是睢一的有力的证据
You have to show it to the police.It’s our only piece of solid evidence.
他们没有看见我挖起它，他们为什么相信是那里挖的
They didn't see me dig it up.Why should they believe it was there?
警察不会为一个79年的陈案，自寻烦恼
The police won't trouble themselves with a 70-year-old case.
它仍是一个悬而未决的谋杀
Still, it's an unsolved murder.
要做的事必须由我去做，我必须去见卡尔迈克尔
Whatever is to be done, has to be done by me. I’ve got to get to Carmichael.
他现在不会见你
他会见我的
- He won't see you now.
- He'll see me.
议员
Senator.
等等，议员
Hold up, Senator.
我是约翰·拉塞尔
I’m John Russell.
议员，看
我想给你看这个
Senator, look.
I want to show him that.
放开
Let go.
看这个，是金质纪念章，上面有你的名字
Look at this. It’s a baptism medal with your name on it.
它与一个小男孩埋在一起
It was buried with the body of a little boy.
警察知道了
The police know about it.
那个疯子是谁
我不知道，不要紧
- Who's that crackpot?
- I have no idea. Never mind.
我要你无线电连接，警察总部德威特上尉
I want you to radio police headquarters. Captain DeWitt.
叫他打我斯泊坎的电话，这个号码
Ask him to call me at Spokane,this number.
你这个婊子养的，你想要什么？
You goddamn son of a bitch.What is it you want?
你想把我怎么样？
What do you want from me?
能做的事我都做了
I’ve done everything I could do.
没有什么要做的
There's nothing more to do.
拉塞尔先生？
Mr. Russell?
我叫德威特上尉
My name is Captain DeWitt.
我想跟你谈谈
行
- I’d like to talk to you.
- All right.
很安静的房子
是的
- Quite a house.
- Yes.
你是作曲家
是的
- You're a composer.
- Yes.
你在大学里教书
没错
- You teach at the university.
- That's right.
这是你装神弄鬼的地方？
你想说什么？
- Is this where you held your seance?
- What do you want to talk about?
你闯入波音飞机的跑道，引起了轩然大波
You were out at Boeing airfield.You caused quite a scene.
大喊，大叫，像个疯子
Screaming, yelling,acting like a lunatic.
我的警官说你昨晚也在做一些奇怪的事
My sergeant tells me you were up to some strange things last night, too.
你在一位女士房子下挖上了一些骨头
You dug up some bones under a lady's house.
某些鬼魂的声音告诉骨头在那
Some ghostly voice told you they were there.
德班警官说你告诉他你不知道骨头是谁
Sergeant Durban said you told him you had no idea who those bones were.
那就有点奇怪了
It seems a little odd then...
...那到处指控控诉议员
...that you go charging about,making accusations about the Senator.
一个为这个州服务了36年的人
A man who has served this state for36 years.
他不会向任何肮脏的敲诈计划屈服
He's not about to give in to any dirty little blackmail scheme.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我理解你失去了妻子和女儿也许你不能释怀
I understand you lost your wife and daughter. Maybe it shook you up.
也许你需要帮忙
我希望你现在离开这里
- Maybe you need help.
- I’d like you to leave now.
我们能替你搞定，你理解我说的话吗?
We can see that you get it.You understand what I’m saying?
出去,现在
听我说,拉塞尔
- Out, now.
- Listen to me, Russell.
你有议员的东西，他想要回去
You've got something of the Senator's.He wants it back.
是块金纪念章,一个传家宝，他认为你拿了
It’s a gold medal. Afamily heirloom.He thinks you've got it.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我很抱歉干涉你，但是我真他妈的疯了...
I’m sorry to barge in on you,but I am so damn mad...
德威特上尉是警察局的
Capt. DeWitt is with the police.
你是诺曼小姐?
是的
- You are Miss Norman?
- Yes.
我一小时内带证据回来我会把这里砸碎
I'll be back in an hour with a warrant and we'll tear this place apart.
怎么了
我会回来
- What's going on?
- I'll be here.
随你便
Suit yourself.
那是怎么回事?
议员认为这是敲诈
- What was that all about?
- The Senator thinks it's blackmail.
他们退了你的租房，他们强迫我辞职
They've cancelled your lease.They've forced me to resign.
没有解释,只有离开
No explanation, just get out.
我必须见董事长，我要知道我能做什么
I have to see the head of the Board of Directors. I'll find out what I can.
我会打电话通知你
I'll call you and let you know.
是的？是的，克菜尔
Yes? Yes, Claire.
我认得这辆车，我不知道怎么会这样
I recognized the car.I don't know how it could've happened.
车子在路中翻了个底朝天，警察死了
The car's upside down in the road and that policeman, he's dead!
有消息吗？
Any messages?
德威特上尉？他说什么了？
Captain DeWitt? What did he say?
什么？
What?
噢 我的天！
Oh my God!
谁？
Who?
拉塞尔？
Russell?
好的，我要那个号码
All right.Let me have that number.
约翰·拉塞尔
议员想见你
- John Russell.
- The Senator is expecting you.
还忙哪
是的
- Still busy?
- Yes.
你去哪儿
我一会儿就回来
- Where are you going?
- I'll be back in a while.
你到底想要什么
我肯定知道点
- What the hell do you want?
- You must have some idea.
真的是他们让我进门的
我是大忙人。有话快说
- They did let me through the door.
- I’m a busy man. Make it fast.
切斯曼公园的房子，1909年以前你家住那儿
The house on Chessman Park.Your family lived there until 1906.
那里发生了一连串怪事
It’s had a history of strange happenings.
那栋房子有东西，鬼魂现身
There's something in that house,a manifestation.
今天下午德威特上尉来见我，是代表你吧
This afternoon, Capt. DeWitt came to see me, presumably on your behalf.
他想必向你汇报了
He must have reported to you.
骚扰，鬼魂现身，井里的尸骨
The disturbances, the seance,the bones found in the well.
在机场我想跟你谈谈
I tried to talk to you at the airport.
我给你看这个
I showed you this.
德威特说你把它掉了
DeWitt said you'd lost it.
我在埋那个孩子的墓里找到的
I found it in the grave where the child was buried.
我现在跟你说的事，无法用逻辑来解释
There's no logical explanation for what I’m going to say to you now.
那个男孩严重残疾
The boy was badly crippled.
我认为他是在房子的阁楼被杀的
I believe he was killed in an attic room of that house.
我看到了
I saw what happened.
我认为是理查德·卡尔迈克尔，你父亲...
I believe it was Richard Carmichael,your father...
...杀了小男孩，他的亲生儿子约瑟夫·卡尔迈克尔
...who murdered the boy,his natural son, Joseph Carmichael.
替身来自一家孤儿院，后来去了欧洲
A substitution from the orphanage was made, and the boy went to Europe.
他被奇迹般地治好了回来继承了帝国
He was cured, miraculously,and returned to inherit an empire.
那个矮小有丑陋的小孩成了你
That changeling was you.
那就是你的故事
随你怎么说
- So, that's your story?
- Whatever you want to call it.
要多少？
我的天！
- How much?
- My God!
你在这里胡闹想要多少钱
How much do you want for this farce?
这不是敲诈
我习惯了跟歹徒打交道
- This isn't blackmail.
- I’m used to dealing with vermin.
你的故事很不可思议
它确实让你害怕
- Your story is so incredible...
- It truly terrifies you.
这是事实，掩埋不了，这不关你事
It’s the truth. It won't be buried.None of this belongs to you!
带着你的肮脏的谎言滚
Get out with your filthy lies.
对那个孩子来说还没有完
It should've gone to that dead child.
你不是约瑟夫·卡尔迈克尔，你是利益谋杀的受益者
You're not Joseph Carmichael. You're the beneficiary of murder for profit.
不!
No!
我父亲不是谋杀者
My father was not a murderer.
没有人可以这么说
Nobody in this world can say that.
我父亲是好人
My father was a great man.
他是个慈爱的人
He was a loving man.
而你来这里控告他...
For you to come in here and accuse him...
...杀人
...of killing.
混蛋
Damn you!
我不会允许你诽谤他的英名
I will not allow you to slander his good name.
这些文件是市档案馆的
These documents are on file in the city.
这是鬼魂现身的录音，没有拷贝
This is a tape of the seance.There's no copy.
拿着吧，要做的我都做了
Take it.I’ve done what I had to do.
对不起
I’m sorry.
拉塞尔...
Russell...
如果我发现你把事情透露出去...
If I find that you've breathed one word of this to anyone...
...你会生不如死
...you'll wish you'd never come into this world.
喊叫声是怎么回事
没什么
- What was all that shouting about?
- Nothing.
出去。让我一个人在这里
Get out. Leave me alone.
约翰？我打过电话
John? I tried to call...
约翰？
John?
你在哪儿？
Where are you?
约翰，你在干什么？
John, what are you doing?
约翰？
John?
约翰，求你，我不想上那儿
John, please,I don't want to come up there.
克莱尔
约翰
- Claire.
- John?
我以为你在这儿
I thought you were here.
我以为你在这儿，我不知道你出去了
I thought you were here.I didn't know you were going out.
在车里等
你不能回去
- Wait in the car.
- You're not going back in there!
我就回来，不要担心
I'll be right back. Don't worry.
约瑟夫，不
Joseph, no!
爸爸
Father.
我的纪念章
My medal!
爸爸
Father!
我的纪念章
My medal.
约翰！
John!
父亲，不
Father, no.
救命
Help.